multisoft.com 2017-09-17

# Privacy Policy • MultiSoft MLM Software

MultiSoft Corporation, together with its subsidiaries (“MultiSoft”) has created this Privacy Policy in line with our commitment to your privacy on MultiSoft websites. The following discloses our information gathering, dissemination and protection practices.

**Compliance**

By accessing this site you agree to the terms of the MultiSoft Corporation Privacy Policy outlined below. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, please do not access or use this site.

**Collection of information**

MultiSoft Corporation collects information to provide better services to our users. We collect information in two ways:

  * information you affirmatively choose to submit to us (such as your name, e-mail address, company name, title, country) for the purpose of accessing various downloads, viewing specific content, subscribing to MultiSoft newsletters, etc.;
  * information we get from your use of our websites, such as the IP address, browser type, ISP, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, number of clicks, domain name and country/state of all visitors to the site; and
  * location information: when you use MultiSoft’s websites, we may collect and process information about your actual location. We use various technologies and tools to determine location.

**Use of information**

Any information collected by MultiSoft will be done in accordance with this privacy policy for the purposes of making better business decisions, supporting the activities you choose to engage in, and providing higher quality solutions and services to our customers. We use your location information to tailor your MultiSoft website experience. We also may use any non-personal information we collect to enhance our website and your IP address for website diagnostics and administration. We will not sell, share, or rent this information, for commercial purposes, to any person or organization. MultiSoft processes information we collect on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your information on a server located outside the country where you live.

**Information security**

MultiSoft treats your personal information as Confidential Information. We protect this confidential Information by storing it on secure servers that only select MultiSoft personnel have access to, and by encrypting it to help prevent access by any unauthorized parties.

**Links**

This website contains links to various third party websites. MultiSoft has no control over and is not responsible for the content, privacy policies or reliability of such sites.

**Changes to the Policy**

MultiSoft reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at its own discretion. The changes can be viewed here or elsewhere at this site. Your continued usage of this site will mean you accept those changes.
